KHOIRONI ARIEF

ABOUT ME

Informatics engineering student at Universitas PGRI Ronggolawe Tuban, interested in programming especially web programming, experienced as a freelance junior web developer, succeeded in creating websites according to client needs. trying to continue to learn and explore programming languages in order to become a professional web developer.

EXPERIENCE

• Dinas Pendidikan Kabupaten Tuban

February 2021 – March 2021

Magang/PKL

Membuat sistem informasi administrasi untuk pencatatan surat keluar dan masuk

• Freelance June 2021 – Now

Web Developer

Membuat website sesuai dengan kebutuhan klien.

EDUCATION

S.kom

August 2018 – September 2022

Universitas PGRI Ronggolawe Tuban

SKILLS

Programming: HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP

Framework: Bootstrap, Codeigniter

DBMS: MySql

Others: GIT, MVC, OOP

Design: Figma, CorelDraw

ORGANIZATIONAL

• Komunitas Seni Rupa Roggolawe

Divisi Publikasi (Desember 2019 – Desember 2020) Mengelola sosial media organisasi, Melakukan dokumentasi kegiatan, dan membuat desain untuk suatu acara. Sekretaris (Desember 2020 – Desember 2021) Melakukan administrasi berupa surat menyurat, membuat proposal, lpj dan lain sebagainya.

• Relawan TIK

Head Of Program and APTIKA (Oktober 2021 – Oktober 2023) Merancang program atau kegiatan bulanan

LANGUAGES

Indonesia: Native Language

English: Novice Listener, Speaker, and Write. Intermediate Reading

PORTOFOLIO

Website: https://khoirony.github.io/

Github: https://github.com/khoirony

Sosmed: https://instagram.com/khoirony_arief/

OTHER

Hobby: Reading and Painting